

Tegar Setio Software Engineer

EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

I am a Software Engineer specializing in Web Development, I have contributed to a wide range of projects, from large-scale initiatives to small business ventures. Currently, I work part-time as a Front-End Engineer at PT. Kreatif Indonesia, and I am also a freelancer on the fastwork platform.

SPECIALIZATIONS

- Html
- Css
- Bootstrap
- Scss
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- React
- Next Js
- Express Js
- Tailwind Css

EDUCATION HIGHLIGHTS

Rakamin Academy

Full Stack Web Development Intensive Bootcamp

Agustus 2023 - Desember 2023

- · understand Introduction to the World of **Programming**
- understand and implement Hml, Css & JavaScript Fundamentals
- understand and implement Version Control
- understand and implement OOP & DOM, Database, Node Js & Rest Full API, Express Js. React Js. Next Js. Final Project **Discussion & Final Presentation**

Tel-U Purwokerto

S1 Teknik Informatika

2021 - Now

CAREER SUMMARY

Freelancer Fastwork

19 August 2023 - Now

Front end Engineer PT.Hudoro Solusi Digital

1 April 2024 - juli 2024

• Front end Engineer PT. Sineas Kreatif Indonesia

1 August 2024 - Now

LISENSI DAN SERTIFIKASI

Sololearn

- Sololearn Certified HTML course May 2022
- Sololearn Certified Css course August 2022

Dicoding

- Belajar Membuat Front-End Web untuk Pemula August 2022
- Belajar Dasar Pemrograman Web August 2022

Rakamin Academy

• Full Stack Web Development Intensive Bootcamp December 2023

Kemdikbud

• Finalis Gemastik September 2023

CONTACT ME

- in Tegar Setio
- +62 882005090497
- tegarsetio02@gmail.com
- https://web-profile-chi.vercel.app/
- Bantarbolang, Kab Pemalang
- kopsus